<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AI Blog</title>
    <link>https://bobmcdear.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AI Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>borna.ahz@gmail.com (Borna Ahmadzadeh)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>borna.ahz@gmail.com (Borna Ahmadzadeh)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bobmcdear.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Attention in Vision</title>
      <link>https://bobmcdear.github.io/posts/attention-in-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>borna.ahz@gmail.com (Borna Ahmadzadeh)</author>
      <guid>https://bobmcdear.github.io/posts/attention-in-vision/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Attention is an influential mechanism in deep learning that has achieved state-of-the-art results in many domains such as natural language processing, visual understanding, speech recognition, multi-modal learning, and more. In this article, popular attention layers in computer vision specifically will be studied and implemented in PyTorch.
Each module is accompanied by detailed descriptions, visualizations, and code, plus optional mathematical formulations for those preferring more formal expositions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bobmcdear.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 13:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>borna.ahz@gmail.com (Borna Ahmadzadeh)</author>
      <guid>https://bobmcdear.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me I am a software developer with a proven track record of delivering complex projects across multiple domains. My areas of expertise cover Python, C/C++, SQL, and Swift, data science and management, machine and deep learning, computer vision, natural language processing, and more. Challenging problems I have tackled in the past include but are not limited to collecting data and developing computer vision models for off-road visual understanding, implementing self-supervised learning techniques to manage data scarcity, employing Bayesian and tree-based models for interpretable personalized healthcare, and deploying machine learning models on a variety of devices under hardware constraints.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
