<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AI Blog</title>
    <link>https://bobmcdear.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AI Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>borna.ahz@gmail.com (Borna Ahmadzadeh)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>borna.ahz@gmail.com (Borna Ahmadzadeh)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bobmcdear.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Attention in Vision</title>
      <link>https://bobmcdear.github.io/posts/attention-in-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>borna.ahz@gmail.com (Borna Ahmadzadeh)</author>
      <guid>https://bobmcdear.github.io/posts/attention-in-vision/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Attention is an influential mechanism in deep learning that has achieved state-of-the-art results in many domains such as natural language processing, visual understanding, speech recognition, multi-modal learning, and more. In this article, popular attention layers in computer vision specifically will be studied and implemented in PyTorch.
Each module is accompanied by detailed descriptions, visualizations, and code, plus optional mathematical formulations for those preferring more formal expositions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bobmcdear.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 13:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>borna.ahz@gmail.com (Borna Ahmadzadeh)</author>
      <guid>https://bobmcdear.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me I am a machine learning developer with specialties covering software development in Python, C/C++, and Swift, data science, machine learning, and deep learning (including related packages such as Scikit-Learn, PyTorch, and ONNX), computer vision, mathematics, and cloud services.
In the past, I have implemented machine learning methods for myriad different tasks, some unseen in academia or industry, and have devised solutions for challenging problems involving too little data, hardware constraints, data drift, interpretablity requirements, et cetera, making me proficient in traditional as well as cutting-edge machine learning branches such as computer vision, self-supervised learning, neural architecture search, Bayesian models, embedded machine learning, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
